torrent-finder.info 2017-06-06

# Torrent Finder Privacy :: Torrent Finder :: Torrent Search Engine

## Torrent Finder Privacy

 **Your Privacy**  
torrent-finder.info is committed to protecting your privacy. torrent-finder.info does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to other companies. torrent-finder.info will not collect any personal information about you except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information.  
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by torrent-finder.info. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post the changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Currently, torrent-finder.info may provide aggregate statistics about our traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personal identifying information.

 **Third Party Advertising**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) .

 **Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

 **Modification of Privacy Policy**  
torrent-finder.info reserves the right, at any time, to modify, alter or update the Privacy Policy and you agree to be bound by such modifications, alterations or updates.
